Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Royal Knight selection exam is now five matches in.
The crystal's magic has been cut off. Team B's the winner!
Ready, full bloom!
Team C wins!
Flame magic! Spiral flame!
Crystal destroyed! Team E wins!
Crystal destroyed! Team G wins!
Picture magic! Twin storms of fire and water!
Sandstone magic! Rock Storm!
Crystal destroyed! Team I wins!
Don't take it too hard, you've got a lot of potential.
But you're a little far away from becoming a masterpiece.
The sixth match is about to begin.
It's finally our turn!
I'll be the leader, no going solo, do you understand me?
We'll give them a performance they'll never forget!
Yeah!
And with that, it's time for match six!
The battle begins now!
Let's go!
Geek, keek, keek, keek, keek, ke vão長aine relatively.
So let's be Magic.
the solve the problems I have without Perdong my mind especially until the end of life ismetendo.
So it'sCOMBOKW isn't the one that has become a genius.
Is it me or not?
So let's go!
We win!
Come run!
Here.
We win!
Thank you.
That was awesome!
Man Run's added some pages to his grimoire and given his power an upgrade.
Lightning magic! Thunderbolt Destruction!
That team's got a strong offense.
Yeah, they're good. And they're only at a junior level, too.
Me and Luck have been cranking out the missions like crazy over the past few months, and every one of them has made us that much more powerful.
So obviously being junior rank doesn't mean a damn thing to us.
They always did have intermediate level talent, and now I see they've continued to improve.
But I've grown as well.
Inspired by Asta, I've trained my magic, my muscles, and my mind.
And my hard work may betray me, but I won't betray my hard work.
Steel magic, fear, spiral, land!
Yeah, no, that's the kind of epic beatdown I'm talking about!
Wow, Klaus, I'm so proud of you!
I suppose you might be more than a bespectacled worry ward after all!
That was pretty cool!
After the tournament's over, would you want to spar with me?
Stop being an incorrigible child and focus on the battle at hand!
That's him. Rob Vitesse. He's turned his back on their crystal.
We should attack all three of them head-on and obliterate their crystal in one blow!
You got it!
Well, look at that. Turns out you silly boys aren't half bad.
Gotcha!
Wait, magic!
Whoa, that lady can fly?
Angel flapping ought to do the trick!
An offensive strike!
Go for it!
And a tailwind for my teammates!
Oh boy, this is a lot of fun!
Now, look! Break it!
The difference in our strengths will determine which of us will emerge victorious!
We threw all that magic at him and the guy didn't budge an inch!
No good!
All right, you crazy kid!
Have at him!
More!
He's fast!
Come on!
Let's fight some more!
What the?
They won with one hit!
Crystal destroyed!
Team K wins!
Way to go!
Yeah, they really showed him, huh?
Woohoo!
That was such a blast!
Oh, look, I can't believe I underestimated you!
That was astounding!
Ding, ding, ladies and gents!
We have a winner!
So, Team K!
I'm so proud!
You did it, look!
That sneaky little rascal!
Damn it!
I think he's too strong!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah ha ha ha!
Next, I'll be fighting him!
Bet that'll be interesting!
I'll paint an even prettier picture!
Now for the eighth and final match of the first round!
Teams O and P!
Approach!
The last one!
And it's a real doozy, too!
I can't wait!
It's gonna be Yuno and Noel on a team together!
Sheesh, that took long enough!
When all this is over with, you owe me a date!
I don't think so.
Who's their third?
Hey, gang!
Are you ready?
If we all do our best, we're sure to make it through this round!
Can you make it through this day?
I just know we're gonna succeed.
Do you think this guy is okay to participate?
Well...
Actually, now that I think about it, didn't you and Osta grow up together?
You'd better not act like an idiot out there like he would.
Same goes for you.
I know magic control isn't your strong suit.
You had your hands full using monoskin back at the volcano.
Are you up for this?
Excuse me?
Don't you realize you're in the presence of royalty?
I mean, let's be honest, you were raised to be a barbarian just like Osta was.
Maybe you're too stupid to participate in this test!
Keep it down, princess!
Not only is that a weak argument, but how you phrased it was childish.
It kind of makes me wonder if Osta's been rubbing off on you.
How dare you!
If you're saying I would let myself be influenced by a mediocre musclehead like Osta,
then you're just as much of an ignorant jerk as he is!
And stop looking at me with that contestant face!
I'm the only one who's allowed to do that to people!
Do you understand me?
Now, now.
You guys aren't being very good sports here.
Don't you think you ought to try to play nice?
I'm pretty sure you're the reason they're arguing, Osta.
Yeah, right!
Who would bother getting angry over you?
Now, I may have to get along with you for this match,
but that doesn't mean I have to like you!
I'm sorry!
Did I say you could touch me?
You must be confident if you've got time for chit-chat.
I'm shocked to find that the shame of how Silva is competing in this tournament.
The Black Bulls may have recently ascended to just above absolute failure,
but you don't consider yourself responsible for that, right?
Can we please not do this?
I'm not surprised you haven't learned to control your magic power.
After all, you couldn't even get accepted into the Silver Eagles,
despite the fact that you were a member of the Silva family.
The jerk with the goofy haircut again, seriously?
What a waste of space.
If you're royalty, then how come you can't do all the amazing things
the rest of our family can, you little freak?
That's odd.
I thought I trained you better than to start eating before I do.
Please give me my time back before you mess it up.
I don't like this game.
If you weren't such a weakling,
then maybe you'd have the ability to protect all the things that are important to you.
Just give it back, okay?
If it makes you angry, then do something about it.
Oh, wait, your dumb spells probably can't hit me, can they?
Oh, great!
That demon raccoon is after you do again!
I was so dead, Parkourine!
My eyeballs are killing me!
It's okay, you can do it, Noel.
Look at how much you've accomplished since you started your journey with the blood balls.
We're cheering for you.
We know what you're capable of better than your brother to his friends and the family you choose.
So, if you can't believe in yourself, then just believe in the friends who believe in you.
Does anybody know what he's mumbling about over there?
I'd say he's putting some kind of unspeakable curse on that Silver Eagles guy.
I think you've wasted enough time.
It's our turn to fight.
Oh, well, I beg your pardon.
I hope you're ready, Noel.
Watch out.
Don't die.
Don't die away, but it's over for you, bud!
And now, the eighth match of round one!
Team O, Alec Dora, Solid, and Dimitri, versus Team P, N, Yuno, and Noel.
Let's begin!
With Noel and Yuno on the same team, I know who's gonna win!
Let you in out!
We're rooting for you!
Show these boys the beautiful babes of the Black Bulls' main business!
Remember not to go easy on him just because he's your big brother!
All the more reason to beat him!
I'll do the attacking.
You two can back me up.
No, that should be my job.
It's fine.
Let me do it!
No, thanks.
Listen here!
I'll be happy on the defensive, actually.
They're a lot faster than I thought.
What's happening?
Vexing as it is to do, this abridged version of that compound magic is a handy shortcut.
A single swift attack, and it's all over!
Their team's crystal is still in its starting location.
Damn.
They're about to shatter ours in one fell swoop.
Wind magic.
Crescent Bye-bye.
Crescent Moonshicle.
Jesus.
Flame magic.
Cambo eruption.
Water magic.
See, dragon?
Fire!
So, the little neophyte thinks she can learn defensive spells, does she?
Sand magic suppressing sand mass!
It's absorbing all the water.
If this keeps up, we'll be stuck on the defensive.
Listen, girl, this is not an opportunity to cozy up my Yuno, okay?
Here's the plan. I'm probably the fastest on the team.
So I'm going to try to catch them off guard and destroy their crystal.
You and that other guy should focus on protecting arms.
Wait. Let me do this.
Please.
I'll stop you right here!
That's the stuff, Noelle!
She's fought alongside Asta.
She'll be fine.
Besides, the crystal's safer with me guarding it.
If it's me who goes.
I've got you now, Noelle.
Solid's sure to be right on my heels.
I said to behave like you're part of the team!
Deal with him later. Fight me.
Hey, did you hear about that four-leaf rookie?
He took down one of the Diamond Kingdom's eight shining generals.
In his first year?
Now that's what I call impressive.
Oh, and it gets better.
After that, he took a shot at the vice-captain and said he'd be the captain of the Golden Dawn.
Just goes to show you, being chosen by the Wind Spear really sets you apart, doesn't it?
Seems like Captain Vongens has high hopes for him.
So you think you can eliminate me and protect your team's crystal at the same time?
There's that arrogance you're so famous for!
Just fight like you mean it, okay?
Why'd it have to be you?
I should have been ready for an ambush.
I managed to escape, but I wound up in this deep cave.
Not much chance of someone coming to save me.
So this is it.
There's no need to fear. I'll help you.
In that moment, he reminded me of a painting from my childhood.
Of a kind and gentle god bathed in a soft light.
I sensed that you were in here.
Your worries are over now.
Besides his magic, Captain Vongens has another strange power.
It's some kind of warmth that connects him to all of us squad members.
After that happened, I swore that I'd dedicate my grimoire to him.
I strove to help the Golden Dawn remain the greatest of all the Magic Knight squads.
Because we are the noble elite, hand-selected by Sir Vongens himself.
So why was he made one of us?
This backwoods commoner?
And what's more...
Even though he bonded with each of us impartially, it's plain to see that the Captain favors him the most.
But why? I don't understand.
You know.
Why has he said that lowlife's name five times today?
And he hasn't spoken the first word to me!
What makes him special?
The four-leaf clover?
It's bad enough that he's regarded so highly above the rest of us.
But for that urchin to declare that he'll become the next Captain of the Golden Dawn?
It's an insult to Sir Vongens!
Don't go getting a big head because you are lucky enough to end up with spirit magic!
It was his amazing power that got him chosen in the first place!
Thank you very much!
Boy, this guy ticks me off! Let's pummel him!
That's enough, Belle.
Seriously? Don't tell me you're thinking about fighting him without letting me help!
Leave it to useless Noel to try to win with one lousy defensive spell!
What's wrong with you?
We were supposed to hit their crystal at the same time, but you just ruined our strategy!
Ah, quiet! What makes you think you get to tell me what to do?
Okay, then. It looks like my only option is to back him up!
Hey!
Huh?
What is that thing?
Fungus magic running Mr. Mushroom.
I sprinkled a few spores on you when you weren't looking.
I'm not letting you stand in Noel's way.
Honestly, I almost feel bad for you.
Any direction you go, I'll be right there.
You don't stand a chance of putting so much as a scratch on my crystal.
Are you sure about that?
Whoa! What's happening here?
Not to worry. It's me, N.
I'm talking to you via my voice transmitting talking mushroom.
You can't go around sticking creepy fungi on people!
I'll make it brief, but please hear me out.
I've been listening to Solid since before the battle began.
The way that monster treats his baby sister is unacceptable.
As the oldest of 11 children, it makes me sick.
In fact, my siblings are the reason I'm fighting today.
Noel, an older brother's most important job is to look after his siblings who are younger and weaker.
But judging by the many hurtful things I've heard him say, it doesn't sound like he's even trying to uphold that responsibility.
So thrash him once and for all!
And I'm not talking about a slap on the wrist! I want you to pulverize this disgrace of a brother!
You've really perked up since the fight started, haven't you?
Humans are like animals! If you put them firmly in their place, they'll never oppose you again!
Oh, this is absolutely hilarious!
Someone's getting thrashed, but it surely won't be me! Sorry!
I can crush you pathetic weaklings without drinking a sweat!
That's right. I was weak before.
And you, Solid. My entire life, you've always been my bigger, stronger, older brother.
But I'm done caring whether or not you approve of me.
I've already earned the approval of people whose opinions matter a lot more than yours!
Once upon a time, I was terrified of what your magic power could do.
But now that just feels silly.
Who cares? You're still a failure!
Water creation magic!
Slashing sea serpent!
Your existence is a slap in my face!
Sand creation magic!
Sand armor!
Dreadnought guard!
This is my most powerful spell!
Offense and defense in one!
Try to stop that without spirit magic!
I will be the one to bring Sarbange's extreme into reality!
Wind magic.
Towering tornado!
From the inside?
Am I crazy or did Yuno somehow activate a spell inside his opponent's magic?
Skills like that and the ladies can't get enough of them?
Damn, this guy really does have it going on!
But that's his dream.
It's not mine.
I only fight for my own dream.
That's absurd!
Insane!
Preposterous!
It's downright impossible!
What even is that magic?
Noelle isn't capable of anything that powerful!
Hey, Solid!
You might...
want a block.
Just try to hit me, you pipsqueak!
She looks strong, but there's no way one of her abilities could ever hurt me!
Do your worst!
You good-for-nothing girl!
Sea Dragon's war!
Awesome!
She won!
She wiped out their crystal in one hit?
Crystal destroyed!
Team P wins!
I'm not weak!
Not anymore!
I don't know.